angloinfo.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

### THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS:

Angloinfo's use of and treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Angloinfo when you are using the Angloinfo website and subsidiaries and when you use services provided by Angloinfo.

  * Angloinfo's use of and treatment of any personally identifiable information that Angloinfo's business partners may share with Angloinfo.

### THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT COVER:

The practices of companies or individuals that Angloinfo does not own or control.

### DATA GATHERING

When you use the Angloinfo site our servers automatically record information that your browser stores and transmits. This may include information such as your:

  * IP address
  * browser type
  * search terms you use
  * websites from which you arrived at ours
  * your activity on our site

We do not match your IP address with any other personally identifiable information except in case of violation of our terms of use.

### PHISHING AND FRAUD

Angloinfo will never ask you to send the following details by email:

  * Your credit card details
  * Bank details
  * Driver's licence details
  * Your full name
  * Your address

If you see an email that looks like it's from us but asks for these details don't reply to it or open any attachments in the email. Delete it and block the sender. We only send emails from two secured domains:

  * @angloinfo.com
  * @anglo.email

You can trust and add to your contacts if you wish anything that comes from these addresses.

### SERVICE PROVIDERS

Angloinfo uses some reliable third parties to provide services to us and to our users. These services and functions include but are not limited to:

  * Billing
  * Customer relationship tools (CRM)
  * Hosting and Maintenance
  * Database storage and management
  * Marketing material production

Angloinfo shares your information with these third parties but only as needed in the normal course of providing services to you and only when these third parties are contractually obliged to uphold the privacy and security of your data.

### COOKIES

A 'cookie' is a small data file downloaded from our website to your computer. There are two kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are temporary and are deleted when you leave the site or disconnect from the Internet. Persistent cookies stay in your web browser to do things like save your password if you visit the site again. To delete persistent cookies follow the instructions given in your web browser's help section. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies but you can instruct your browser not to accept them. We use cookies to collect data on how you use our website and to improve our service to you. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Angloinfo may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the site and our services to improve the site and our services and to track aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the site.

### MARKETING

We may use your contact information to market to you and/or provide you with information about our products and services and/or the products and services of our partners. If you no longer wish to receive these emails please follow the unsubscribe process in the footer of the emails or contact abuse@angloinfo.com

### COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS AND LAW ENFORCEMENT

Angloinfo cooperates with government and law enforcement officials. We reserve the right to share any information we have about you with government or law enforcement officials. The decision to share this information will be at the sole discretion of Angloinfo to protect the property and rights of Angloinfo or a third party the personal safety of any person to prevent or stop any illegal unethical or legally actionable activity or to comply with the law in any other way.

### SECURITY

Angloinfo is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We take all appropriate physical and electronic measures to ensure that we keep your information secure and that we only keep it as long as is reasonable and necessary. We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security confidentiality or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on our site in the shortest time possible and without unreasonable delay consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. Although we use appropriate security measures once we have received your personal information the transmission of information over the internet is never completely secure. We do our best to protect personal information but we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted to our website so any transmission is at the user's own risk. Angloinfo treats all the information it holds with the utmost care and security. Personal details are stored on our system in an encrypted format that can only be accessed when you place an order using your username or email address and password. Any payment card details (such as credit or debit cards) are passed securely to our world-leading payment processing provider Stripe.com and is in accordance to the Payment Card Industry Security Standards.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our site contains links to other websites. A link is not an endorsement of that third party website and you use any third party sites at your own risk. Angloinfo encourages you to read the privacy statements of the other websites you visit to become informed of their practices and policies.

### FUTURE CHANGES:

Angloinfo may edit or alter this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any substantial changes will be notified via email or a prominent announcement on our site.

### QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS

If you have questions or suggestions please send an email to privacy@angloinfo.com.
